Hello everyone, this is Rena Nakamura, a 3rd term student.
We're in the middle of the production of "Ending Shock.
I'd like to take some pictures of our routine before the show starts.
I'm always messing around with the members.
So I don't usually take pictures by myself.
I don't know how it will turn out.
I don't know how it will turn out, but for now, I'd like to take some routine shots today.
I'm not sure how it will turn out.
Yes, sir.
There's a board that you turn when you arrive at the studio.
The first thing you have to do when you arrive is to return this board.
Surprisingly, this kind of thing is not done at live performances, so it may be rare to see something like this.
Here's what I'm wearing today.
It's a shock jersey, a company jersey.
It has the logo here, and I'm wearing the top and bottom.
It's a little hard to show.
It's a little short, but it looks like this.
It's a little short, but it's got the logo on the back.
There's a big logo on the back like this.
This jersey is not for sale.
So this is a very rare jersey.
I'm going to take good care of it.
This is how it looks like!
Today I arrived at Ransha's dressing room.
I'll introduce you... Basically, the dressing room is all tatami mats.
Yes, tatami mats. This is a stretch ball.
I use it for close-ups.
I've been doing that for a while now.
So I thought I'd give you a little boost.
So I thought I'd give it a little boost.
I put a diffuser in the room and enjoy it like at home.
And yes, I'm sure I left that script there.
I've done two films now, so sometimes I lose track.
I sometimes lose track of what I'm supposed to say.
There are scripts and scores.
It's amazing. It's so thick.
It's this thick.
All of this, all of this, all of this, all of this, all of this, all of this, all of this, all of this.
I'm looking back at it like this...
It's divided into parts for the chorus, so you can keep it in case you get lost.
This is a pamphlet...
This is a pamphlet.
I'd like you all to take a look at them.
I'd like you all to take a look at them here.
I heard you can look at it from this side and the other side from the main story.
I'd like you all to take a look.
Next, I'm going to show you that most of the makeup is done on stage.
I have my hair done, but my face is basically my own.
But for this role, I was told that I didn't have to make it too strong.
I tried to make it look as natural as possible, but still make the parts clearly visible.
I always try to make it look as natural as possible, but at the same time make sure that the parts of the face are clearly visible.
I'm a bit bored with my makeup, so I don't use a lot of different things, so it's not like I do this makeup every day.
I don't use it every day, but as a base.
I often use these two for the base.
If I do a swatch like this, it looks like I'm just lying down.
It looks like I'm just lying down, doesn't it?
All you have to do is lie down.
So it's very good.
Oh, yeah, I changed my clothes.
This is after you've had your hair and stuff done.
So that after they do my hair and stuff, I can change out of the costume without my hair falling out.
It's an easy, lazy outfit.
If I show it like this...
It really looks like home, doesn't it?
Like pajamas.
The show starts in an hour.
Like that...
It's really like this in real life.
Even though we're doing this until the last minute.
Lazy, lazy, lazy.
It's a good time to swatch.
Now, it's 11:58.
The make-up artist will be here in a little over 10 minutes.
I'm going to finish my face.
I'm going to make it!
With my usual hair slope, it really looks like this.
I did apply a little glitter earlier, but...
That's about it.
The base is already made.
I'm applying Mac's Small Eyeshadow Suspiciously Sweet.Oh, the one I'm applying now will be Mac's Small Eyeshadow Suspiciously Sweet.
And I'm going to apply it like this.
You know what I mean? This one.
No, you know what? Maybe you girls get it.
I'm afraid I'm going to have to get up a little early here.
Look at this.
Like this.
I hope it's okay.
I'm already doing this every day.
I don't know what's going on.
I think my face looks like this.
Finished!
My hair looks like this.
I'm done!
But this was 30 minutes ago.
I have to go get a microphone and change my clothes.
Surprisingly, before the show starts, things are very busy, and you think you'll have time to relax and spend some time, but you don't have time.
But I didn't have time to relax, and I was in trouble later on.
I'm in a hurry when I start to feel everyone's first glance.
Hey, you!
I changed my clothes.
I have a lot of costumes to wear a dress
I'm going to take out some of these highlights
I'm gonna take out a little bit of this highlight.
Just a little bit.
I'm going to put it in here.
To make it look shiny.
I'm wearing it.
You can see my hair like this.
And the outfit is like this.
This is the opening outfit for the first song.
It's only one song, but it's such a nice dress.
It looks like this.
The next preview
Yes, we've just finished the first act, and we're taking a 30-minute break before the second act.
I've been fixing my hair for about 10 minutes now.
Actually, I'm straightening and fixing my hair here.
So, yes, I have 20 minutes left, maybe 15 minutes.
That's good.
I'm filming like this, like a pre-stage routine right now.
But up to this point, like this piece.
I've never been in a show where I dance and move my body like this.
I've never been in a show where I'm dancing and moving around like this.
So I'm spending my time in a way that is a little bit unusual.
Well, I'm off to eat two questions.
It's over.
It's over. The colors of the city are over.
But in an hour and a half, we'll be at Eternal.
I'm sorry, but I'm a little nervous right now because I took my hair out.
Yes, sir.
I'm in the audience now.
I'm here.
I'm in the front row, right in front of the orchestra pit.
I'm in seat 0.
Look, it's amazing.
This is what the view looks like.
I can see more than you think. I can see the expressions on your faces.
Oh, my gosh, this is the center. Look over there.
Wow!
I can't show you this on the stage right now, but it's so close!
It's like this!
Lunch!
We got bento!
Wow, it's great!
Bon appétit!
Mmm! Mmm!
Mmm-hmm.
I feel like I'm always backstage.
I'm always backstage with the other members.
It's strange to be alone.
But, you know...
But, you know, in this fixed area, everyone is active in various fields, like Ume was in "Kingdom" just a few days ago.
I'm impressed by the fact that everyone here is active in various fields, and I'm thinking that I have to do my best, too.
I have a lot of personal goals for this year, and since I have a lot of younger students, we are all working together to achieve them.I have a lot of personal goals for this year.
I would like to get to know them better. I would like to get to know the 5th graders better, too.
I want to talk with them.
I have always said that I personally like Aya Ogawa a lot.
I personally like Aya Ogawa a lot. I want to see her.
I'm always sneaking a peek at her, thinking how cute she is. Always behind the scenes.
I want to make lots of memories with everyone. I'll do my best.
Okay, I'm dressed now, as if I've earned it.
It's early, the show is already starting.
Eternal is wearing this white dress, right?
It's like this.
I'm off to the show.
Bye bye!
The ending.
I don't know if it's going to be okay.
The video of what they're doing during the intermission is the same as before.
I thought it was the same, so I changed the camera position and direction, but it's probably the same.
I changed the camera position and direction, but it's probably the same.
Okay, I'm off to get ready for the second act.
Good night!
Well, I'm really tired today.
I think we did it!
We did two shows!
I'm tired.
I'm shaggy.
I always come home exhausted like this.
Okay. So...
It was a routine for a day of singing.
Well, it's always been like this.
I'm sure everyone wonders what I do for half an hour between the first and second acts.
I always wondered what you guys were doing for 30 minutes between acts 1 and 2.
When I was on the audience side.
I used to wonder about that when I was on the audience side.
I thought, "Well, this is how I spend my time...
Well, it's a bit loose.
I hope you enjoy it.
I've never done two months before.
I'm always wondering if it's going to be okay.
Whenever I open my mouth.
I've always had a lot of disquiet.
But as I've done it every day...
I was really, really impressed.
I'm really impressed with this work.
I'm really happy to be able to be a part of such a work.
I never thought I would be able to work on such a work
I never thought I'd be able to work on such a work.
I think that this experience
I think it was a big, big experience.
There are still a few days left.
I will do my best.
I hope all of you who are coming from now on
Please enjoy yourselves!
That's all for now, this is Reina Nakamura.
Bye bye!
Please subscribe to our channel and rate us highly!